<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="Upgrading Liferay projects to Liferay Portal 6.2">
   <taskGroup kind="choice" name="Upgrading Liferay projects to Liferay Portal 6.2" skip="false">
      <intro>
         This cheat sheet will guide you through the individual steps necessary to update Liferay portlets, hooks, layout templates, themes to the latest version of Liferay Portal version 6.2.
<br/>
<br/>
To assist you along the way, wizards and commands
         will be available for you to launch automatically.  If at any time you run into issues, please visit the Liferay IDE forums url listed below:<br/>
<br/>
http://www.liferay.com/community/forums/-/message_boards/category/4627757
      </intro>
      <onCompletion>
         Congratulations!  You have just updated your projects to Liferay Portal 6.2.  For any issues please visit the Liferay IDE community forums page listed below and post a new thread with any issues encountered.

http://www.liferay.com/community/forums/-/message_boards/category/4627757
      </onCompletion>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Backup sources" skip="true">
         <intro>
            Before starting the upgrade process you should backup and
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            You are now ready to begine the upgrade process.
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="upgrade/backup.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Create Liferay Portal 6.2 runtime and server" skip="false">
         <intro>
            You must have a valid Liferay Portal 6.2 Runtime and Server properly configured to upgrade plugin projects to 6.2
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b>
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="upgrade/runtime-server.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Upgrading portlet projects" skip="false">
         <intro>
            This cheat sheet will walk you through all of the steps necessary to upgrade your Liferay portlet projects to use Liferay Portal 6.2.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Congratulations!</b> You have not finished upgrading your Liferay portlet projects to Liferay Portal 6.2
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="upgrade/portlets.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Upgrading hook projects" skip="false">
         <intro>
            This cheat sheet will walk you through all of the steps necessary to upgrade your Liferay hooks projects to use Liferay Portal 6.2.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Congratulations!</b> You have not finished upgrading your Liferay hook  projects to Liferay Portal 6.2
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="upgrade/hooks.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Upgrading layout templates" skip="false">
         <intro>
            This cheat sheet will walk you through all of the steps necessary to upgrade your Liferay layout templates to use Liferay Portal 6.2 bootstrap style layout templates.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Congratulations!</b> You have not finished upgrading your layout templates to Liferay Portal 6.2
         </onCompletion>
         <param name="path" value="upgrade/layout-templates.xml">
         </param>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Deploy upgraded projects to 6.2 server" skip="false">
         <intro>
            <b>Introduction</b>
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            <b>Conclusion</b>
         </onCompletion>
      </task>
   </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet>
